A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A97), 1966, 1969-1997, 2004; bulk; 1.23; 129.6 Cubic Feet; 108 record cartons. Boxes R2965-R3072.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 92020 A 33 - MOVEMENT THEATRE INTERNATIONAL, INC. - WATER PUPPETS OF VIETNAM, 1991-1993 (Box R3037)
    - RF 92020 A35 - BOSTON DANCE UMBRELLA - NATIVE AMERICAN FESTIVAL, 1989-1993 (Box R3037)
    - RF 92020 A 37 - LOUISVILLE ORCHESTRA, INC. - SOUNDCELEBRATION II, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R3037)
    - RF 92020 A 38 - FESTIVAL INTERNATIONAL DE LOUISIANE - 1992 INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL ACTIVITIES, 1991-1994 (Box R3037)
    - RF 92020 A 39 - HENSON FOUNDATION - PARTICIPATION OF DIABLO MUNDO IN INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF PUPPET THEATRE, 1991-1994 (Box R3038)
    - RF 92020 A 40 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - NATIONAL THEATRES OF AZTLAN (TENAZ) FESTIVAL, CONFERENCE, PLAYWRITE COMPETITION, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R3038)
    - RF 92020 A 42 - NATIONAL BLACK ARTS FESTIVAL, INC. - NEW PLAY PROJECT AND INTERNATIONAL ARTISTS FOR 1992 FESTIVAL, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R3038)
    - RF 92020 A 45 - NEW YORK SHAKESPEARE FESTIVAL - "MADNESS CONTINUES" FESTIVAL, 1992-1993 (Box R3038)
    - RF 92020 A 46 - THEATER FOR THE NEW CITY - CIRCUIT EARTH NETWORK EGO-FESTIVAL ACTIVITIES, 1992-1993, 1996; 2 folders. (Box R3038)
    - RF 92029 - QUASI-MILITARY YOUTH CORPS - DOMESTIC SERVICE CORPS FOR SCHOOL DROPOUTS, 1989-1994 (Box R3038)
    - RF 92029 A 1 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - OUT-OF-SCHOOL YOUTH STUDY, 1991-1994 (Box R3039)
    - RF 92029 A 2 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - NATIONAL SERVICE FOR OUT-OF-SCHOOL YOUTH, 1989-1996 (Box R3039)
    - RF 92029 A 2 - CENTER FOR STRATEGIC AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - NATIONAL SERVICE FOR OUT-OF-SCHOOL YOUTH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3039)
    - RF 92031 - NATIONAL OPINION RESEARCH CENTER- SEXUAL BEHAVIOR DATA, 1990-1995 (Box R3039)
    - RF 92034 A 359 - INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK - TENTH ANNUAL MEETING, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R3040)
    - RF 92034 A 359 - INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK - TENTH ANNUAL MEETING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3040)
    - RF 92034 A 361 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FACULTY OF MEDICINE CURRICULUM REVIEW WORKSHOP, 1992-1996 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92034 A 364 - UNIVERSITY OF YAOUNDE (CAMEROON) ? COMPUTERS FOR CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92034 A 366 - INCLEN - PROGRAM COMMITTEE MEETINGS, 1992-1994 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92035 A 6 - BOSTON UNIVERSITY - VACCINE DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, 1992-1996 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 267 - SATTI, KAMAL - ADIA - REHABILITATION OF FARMS IN SUDAN, 1992-1993, 1996-1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 269 - DIENE, SERIGNE - ADIA: CHILD FEEDING PRACTICES IN SENEGAL, 1992-1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 273 - OJUKUTU-MACAULEY, SYLVIA- ADIA: WOMEN, POWER AND CHANGE IN SIERRA LEONE, 1992-1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 277 - DIAGNE, ALIOU - ADIA: AGRICULTURAL HOUSEHOLDS IN SENEGAL, 1992-1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 280 - AFRICAN ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - AWARDEES RETURN TO AFRICA, 1987-1994 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 281 - LELO, FRANCIS- ADIA: HUMANIZATION OF WILDLIFE MANAGEMENT IN KENYA, 1991-1994 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 297 - KILO, MARGARET - ADIA: "GENDER DIFFERENCES IN ACCESS TO SCHOOLING IN CAMEROON", 1992-1994, 1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 309 - BUSIA, AWA - ADIA: PREFERENTIAL FLOW IN SOILS, 1992-1994 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92038 A 324 - SHETTIMA, KOLE- ADIA: PARTICIPATORY DEVELOPMENT IN RURAL NIGERIA, 1992-1997 (Box R3041)
    - RF 92040 A 85 - STATE DANCE ASSOCIATION OF FLORIDA INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1989-1993; 2 folders. (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 1 - INSTITUTE FOR PUERTO RICAN POLICY - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1989-1996 (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 2 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1993 (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 3 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1992, 1995 (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 4 - MIDWEST/NORTHEAST VOTER REGISTRATION EDUCATION PROJECT - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1991-1992 (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 5 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF COLORED PEOPLE (SPECIAL CONTRIBUTION FUND) - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1992, 1995 (Box R3042)
    - RF 92047 A 6 - NORFOLK STATE UNIVERSITY - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1991-1994 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92047 A 7 - PUERTO RICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND- REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1994 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92047 A 10 - SOUTHWEST VOTER REGISTRATION EDUCATION PROJECT - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92047 A 11 - SOUTHWEST VOTER RESEARCH INSTITUTE - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1990-1993 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92047 A 12 - CENTER FOR CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES, 1992-1994 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92047 A 13 - LEADERSHIP CONFERENCE EDUCATION FUND - REDISTRICTING AND REAPPORTIONMENT, VOTING RIGHTS, 1990-1993 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92050 - WNYC FOUNDATION - "TEEN CITY" PROGRAM, 1990-1994 (Box R3043)
    - RF 92051 - FUND FOR THE CITY OF NEW YORK ? COMMUNITY COURT IN TIMES SQUARE AREA, 1991-1995 (Box R3044)
    - RF 92060 A 13 - UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF NORTH WALES - CONFERENCE ON MOLECULAR MARKERS IN SORGHUM AND PEARL MILLET, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box R3044)
    - RF 92061 - INTERNATIONAL IRRIGATION MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE / INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (IIMI/IRRI), 1989-1996 (Box R3044)
    - RF 92061 - INTERNATIONAL IRRIGATION MANAGEMENT INSTITUTE / INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (IIMI/IRRI) - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3044)
    - RF 92072 A 125 - FILM SOCIETY OF LINCOLN CENTER, INC. - FESTIVAL LATINO: "NEW TRENDS IN MEXICAN CINEMA, PART II", 1993 (Box R3044)
    - RF 92072 A 126 - INTERNATIONAL FILM SEMINARS, INC. - 1993 ROBERT FLAHERTY SEMINAR ON LATIN AMERICAN MEDIA ARTS, 1993-1994; 4 folders. (Box R3044)
    - RF 92077 A 56 - BOSTON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1995; 5 folders. (Box R3045)
    - RF 92077 A 56 - BOSTON FOUNDATION - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3046)
    - RF 92092 A 47 - AIDS SOCIETY OF ASIA AND THE PACIFIC - INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS ON AIDS, 1992-1993 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92092 A 51 - AIDS COUNCELLING TRUST (ACT) - THIRD CONFERENCE OF SOUTHERN AFRICAN NETWORK OF AIDS SERVICE ORGANIZATIONS, 1992-1995 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92092 A 52 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC HEALTH (MEXICO) - COMMERCIAL SEX WORKERS AND HIV TRANSMISSION, 1990-1993 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92092 A 57 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR INTERNATIONAL HEALTH - WORKSHOP: PVO AGENDAS REGARDING HIV/AIDS, 1993 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92092 A 58 - CHIANG MAl UNIVERSITY - THAI MILITARY MALE HEALTH STUDY, 1990-1997 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92093 A 3 - RESOURCES DEVELOPMENT FOUNDATION (RFD) - FEASIBILITY STUDIES OF RENEWABLE & WASTEWATER CONVERSION PROJECTS, 1991-1994 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92093 A 4 - ARTHUR ANDERSEN ECONOMIC CONSULTING - DEMAND-SIDE MANAGEMENT PROGRAMS, 1992-1996 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92094 A 23 - FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS - HARARE MEETING, 1993-1996 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92094 A 32 - PLANET 21 - DISTRIBUTION OF PEOPLE & THE PLANET ON EDUCATING GIRLS TO AFRICAN EDUCATORS, 1991-1995 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92095 A 29 - HANDSPRING TRUST FOR PUPPETRY IN EDUCATION (SOUTH AFRICA) - PUPPETRY TO TEACH SCIENCE, 1992-1994 (Box R3047)
    - RF 92099 A 98 - ARTS COMPANY - "THE BOSTON PROJECT", 1993-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 99 - BROOKLYN ACADEMY OF MUSIC - DANCE WORK BY SARDANO, 1993-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 101 - O'NEILL MEMORIAL THEATER CENTER - MARCO POLO PROJECT, 1992-1993 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 103 - WALKER ART CENTER - "THE HEART IN EXILE", 1992-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 104 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - "LIFEDANCE III", 1992-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 105 - REICH MUSIC FOUNDATION, INC. - "THE CAVE" MUSIC/THEATERNIDEO WORK, 1989-1995 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 106 - PERFORMING ARTSERVICES - "A MIRACLE OF CARS", 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 107 - LA PENA CULTURAL CENTER, INC. "STREET STORIES", 1992-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 109 - FRIENDS OF THE DAVIS CENTER, INC. - "THE SHADOW CATCHERS"/"MY DARLING GREMLIN", 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 111 - BYRD DANCE FOUNDATION, INC. ? DANCE/PERFORMANCE WORKS, 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 112 - CULTURAL ODYSSEY- "WOMEN SAVING THEIR OWN LIVES", 1992-1993 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 113 - BRAVA FOR WOMEN IN THE ARTS - "ARTHUR AND LEILA", 1992-1994 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 115 - AMERICAN INDIAN COMMUNITY HOUSE, INC. - "ONE PEOPLE/MANY CULTURES", 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 116 - TEATRO CAMPESINO - "EL BAILE DE LOS GIGANTES", 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 117 - DISTRICT CURATORS, INC. - MULTIWORKS PROJECT, 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 118 - CIRCLE REPERTORY CO., INC. - "WIDESCREEN VERSION OF THE WORLD", 1992, 1996 (Box R3048)
    - RF 92099 A 119 - WORLD MUSIC INSTITUTE, INC.- MUSIC AND DANCE COLLABORATION, 1992, 1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92099 A 120 - BLOOMSBURG THEATRE ENSEMBLE, INC. - "UNDER AFRICAN SKIES", 1992-1994 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92099 A 121 - CAPOEIRA FOUNDATION, INC. - "PIVETE", 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92099 A 123 - TARA ARTS GROUP, LTD. - "THE ODYSSEY: AN ASIAN SONG-LINE", 1992-1995 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 49 - AMERICAN MUSIC THEATER FESTIVAL, INC. - NEW WORKS AT CROSSCURRENTS FESTIVAL, 1992-1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 50 - KINGS MAJESTIC CORP. - WORLD ART FESTIVAL, 1992-1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 53 - PREGONES TOURING PUERTO RICAN THEATRE COLLECTION, INC.- 1993 TEATRO FESTIVAL, 1992-1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 55 - INTERNATIONAL THEATRE FESTIVAL OF CHICAGO - MEETING OF FESTIVAL PRESENTERS, 1992-1995 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 56 - TEATRO AVANTE, INC. - HISPANIC THEATRE FESTIVAL, 1988-1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92100 A 56 - TEATRO AVANTE, INC. - HISPANIC THEATRE FESTIVAL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3049)
    - RF 92121 A 34 - ASSOCIATION FOR SUPERVISION AND CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT - FIRST COMER SATELLITE BROADCAST, 1992-1996 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92123 - SCIENTISTS' INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC INFORMATION (SIPI) - INCREASE PUBLIC UNDERSTANDING OF SCIENCE, 1992-1993 (Box R3049)
    - RF 92124 - PUBLIC TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE, INC. (AMERICAN PLAYHOUSE) - NONPROFIT FUND FOR INDEPENDENT FILMS, 1992-1995 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93001 A 176 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY AND GENETIC ENGINEERING OF RICE, 1993-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93001 A 178 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - WORKSHOP ON CAROTENOID BIOSYNTHESIS IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1993-1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 174 - RESEARCH LABORATORY FOR AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY AND BIOCHEMISTRY (RLABB) (NEPAL) - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY AND GENOME ANALYSIS, 1992-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 175 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY - GENE TRANSFER OF RICE, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 179 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - VISITING SCIENTIST RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP FOR TIAN WENZHONG, 1992-1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 186 - INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP ON STRATEGIES FOR INTRODUCING APOMIXIS IN RICE, 1991-1995 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 191 - WANG JUN- GENETIC ENGINEERING OF RICE FOR PATHOGEN RESISTANCE, 1989-1993 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 199 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - BACILLUS THURINGIENSIS AGAINST YELLOW STEM BORER, 1991-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93003 A 201 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (TNAU)- FUSION OF INDICA AND JAPONICA RICE, 1992-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93005 A 10 - SCOTT-WENDT, JOHN, 1989-1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93009 A 4 - POPULATION INSTITUTE - NGO PREPARATORY MEETING FOR UN POPULATION CONFERENCE, 1993, 1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93009 A 8 - ENVIRONNMENT AND POPULATION CENTRE (ZAMBIA) - WORKSHOP ON WOMEN'S PERSPECTIVES ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1993-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93009 A 13 - EQUIUBRES ET POPULATIONS (FRANCE) - SYMPOSIUM ON WORLD POPULATION ISSUES, 1993-1994 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93009 A 14 - ADEOKUN, LAWRENCE A. - EXPENSES: UNPF/UNESCO MEETING - SOCIOCULTURAL FACTORS AFFECTING DEMOGRAPHY, 1993-1996 (Box R3050)
    - RF 93013 A 527 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1983-1993 (Box R3051)
    - RF 93017 A 102 - ARTS COMPANY, INC.- REDISTRICT CALIFORNIA/HAWAII COMPONENT OF REGIONAL INITIATIVE PROGRAM, 1992-1993 (Box R3051)
    - RF 93027 A 385 - INTERNATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGICAL ASSOCIATION - XIII INTERNATIONAL SCIENTIFIC MEETING, 1992-1993 (Box R3051)
    - RF 93027 A 390 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - STUDY ON TUBERCULOSIS CHEMOTHERAPY AT MULAGO HOSPITAL, 1992-1997 (Box R3051)
    - RF 93027 A 397 - INCLEN, INC. - ELEVENTH ANNUAL MEETING, 1992-1993; 2 folders. (Box R3051)
    - RF 93027 A 397 - INCLEN, INC. - ELEVENTH ANNUAL MEETING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3051)
  - Fellowships (F)
    Arranged alphabetically, by last name of fellowship recipient.
    - F-AS NEPAL - ADHIKARI, TIKA B., 1991-1993 (Box R3052)
    - F-AS KOREA - AHN, SANG NAG, 1986-1993 (Box R3052)
    - F-AS INDIA - ANURATHA, C. S., 1989-1993 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS SIERRA LEONE - BAH, SULAIMAN MALADOH, 1990-1993 (Box R3052)
    - F-AS CHINA - BAI SHUNONG, 1990-1994 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS FRANCE - BARBIERI, MAGALI, 1989-1991 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS GHANA - BENEFO, KOFI DARKWA, 1987-1994 (Box R3052)
    - F-AS BANGLADESH - BISWAS, GADAB CHANDRA GHOSH, 1990-1995 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - BITTO, ADENIKE COKER, 1991-1994 (Box R3052)
    - F-AS ZIMBABWE - BONGA, JULIA, 1989-1992 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS COLOMBIA - BOTERO ARISMENDY, LUIS FERNANDO, 1989-1991 (Box R3052)
    - F-HS LAOS - BOUNPHENG PHILAVONG, 1990-1993 (Box R3052)
    - F-PS NEW ZEALAND - BREWIS, ALEXANDRA A., 1990-1992 (Box R3053)
    - F-PS MEXICO - CARDENAS ELIZALDE, MARIA DEL ROSARIO, 1991-1993 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS MALAWI - CHALIRA, ZAKIA R. G., 1989-1994 (Box R3053)
    - F-PS INDIA - CHATURVEDI, PRADEEP KUMAR, 1990-1994 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN - CHAUDHRY, BUSHRA, 1992-1994 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS CHINA - CHEN DAN, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R3053)
    - F-PS CHINA - CHEN, MING-DAO, 1989-1991, 1994, 1997 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS CHINA - CHEN MINGSHUN, 1987-1991, 1994-1996 (Box R3053)
    - F-PS CHINA - CHEN YI, 1987-1991 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS INDIA - CHOUDHURY, VIJAY KUMAR, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box R3053)
    - F-PS TAIWAN - CHU, CHIN YI CYRUS, 1990-1992 (Box R3053)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - CRUZ, ROLANDO T., 1988-1990, 1994 (Box R3053)
    - F-HS BRAZIL - DOS REIS, MITERMAYER GALVAO, 1985-1989 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS INDIA - DUIT, ADITI, 1988-1992 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS CHINA - FANG XUE-GUANG, 1987-1991 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS UNITED STATES - FEIFER, CHRISTINE, 1989-1992, 1995 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS BENIN - GANDAHO, TIMOTHEE, 1992-1994 (Box R3054)
    - F-HS NIGERIA - GBENLE, GEORGE OLABODE, 1986-1988 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS INDIA - GHOSH, PRADIP K., 1988-1994 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS CHINA - GU YANMIN, 1989-1992 (Box R3054)
    - F-AS CHINA - GU YONG-GIANG, 1986-1995 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS UNITED STATES - GUHL, NORA LOUISE, 1984-1992 (Box R3054)
    - F-PS CHINA - HE ZHIGANG, 1989-1995 (Box R3054)
    - F-AS KOREA - KIM DONGHERN, 1988-1994 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS KOREA - KIM JU-KON, 1987-1993 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS KOREA - KIM TAE SAN, 1986-1992 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS INDIA - KISHOR, SUNITA, 1991-1994 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS CAMEROON - KUATE DEFO, BARTHELEMY, 1988-1995 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS ECUADOR - IZQUIERDO JIMENEZ, CESAR ANTONIO, 1991-1993 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS INDIA - JENA, KSHIROD KUMAR, 1989-1996 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS CHINA - JIANG JIPING, 1988-1994 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS INDIA - JOSE BENNY, 1991-1992 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS INDIA - JUNEJA, RENU, 1991-1993 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS INDIA - KAPOOR, RAJIV KUMAR, 1992-1993 (Box R3055)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN - KHAN, ESTHER, 1991-1993 (Box R3055)
    - F-PS US - KUMAR, ANURADHA, 1990-1993 (Box R3056)
    - F-AS INDIA - KUMARAVADIVEL, NACHIMUTHU G., 1990-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS INDIA - LAKSHMANASAMY, THANGAMUTHU, 1991-1992 (Box R3056)
    - F-HS INDIA - LAL, RENU BANSAL, 1985-1987 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS CHILE - LEYTON, LISETTE, 1989-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS CHINA - LIANG, ZHI-GUO, 1988-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS CHINA - LIN JIANG, 1988-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS CHINA - LIU XIAN, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS MEXICO - LOPEZ-RIOS, OLGA, 1988-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS US - MCKINNEY, BARBARA J., 1990-1993 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS INDIA - MAJUMDAR, NANDITA, 1989-1994 (Box R3056)
    - F-AS ZAIRE - MATUNGULU, KANDE MUTANDA, 1987-1993 (Box R3056)
    - F-AS INDIA - MAWAL, YOGESH RAMSWARUP, 1989-1993 (Box R3056)
    - F-PS USA - MILLER, TIMOTHY WILLIAM, 1992-1993 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS INDIA - MOHANTY, PRASANNA KUMAR, 1991-1992 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS CHILE - MOORE, GRACE D., 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS NEPAL - NIRAULA, BHANU BHAKTA, 1992-1995 (Box R3057)
    - F-HS UGANDA - NTAMBI, JAMES MUKASA, 1984-1987 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - NWAKEZE, PETER C., 1988-1991 (Box R3057)
    - F-AS ZIMBABWE - NZIMA, MUNTUBANI D. S., 1988-1994 (Box R3057)
    - F-AS THAILAND - ORADY, TANPATTA-ANUN, 1989-1992 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - OYELOLA, OLADAYO OYEYIOLA, 1991-1995 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS INDIA - PANCHAL, REKHA GANPAT, 1990-1991 (Box R3057)
    - F-AS THAILAND - PATCHARA VERAKALASA, 1990-1992 (Box R3057)
    - F-PS ARGENTINA - PONCE, RUBEN H., 1989-1994 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS CHINA - QIU YILAN, 1989-1994 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS ARGENTINA - ROFMAN, RAFAEL P., 1990-1993 (Box R3058)
    - F-AS INDIA - ROUT, JYOTI R., 1989-1994 (Box R3058)
    - F-AS INDIA - SADANANDA, A. R., 1990-1993 (Box R3058)
    - F-AS INDIA - SAKTHIVEL, NATARAJAN, 1990-1995 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS JAPAN - SAKURAGI NORIAKI, 1990-1993 (Box R3058)
    - F-AS INDIA - SAMIYAPPAN, RAMASAMY, 1990-1993 (Box R3058)
    - F-AS IVORY COAST - SANGARE, ABDOURAHAMA, 1990-1994 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS ETHIOPIA - SEBHAT AFEWORK, 1990-1993 (Box R3058)
    - F-HS USA - SHAPIRO, THERESA A. B., 1985-1987 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS INDIA - SHARIFF, ABUSALEH, 1991-1992 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS CHINA - SHI CON-ZHU, 1990-1995 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS INDIA - SHREENIWAS, SUDHA, 1990-1992 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS TANZANIA - SICHONA, FRANCIS JOSEPH, 1990-1992 (Box R3058)
    - F-PS INDIA - SINGH, SHIO KUMAR, 1989-1992 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS INDIA - SRIVASTAVA, RAJESH K., 1989-1995 (Box R3059)
    - F-AS ZIMBABWE - SUKUME, CHRISPEN, 1989-1992 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS CHILE - SZASZ PIANTA, IVONNE ROSA, 1989-1992 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - TOGUNDE, RASHEED OLADIMEJI, 1991-1995 (Box R3059)
    - F-AS ZIMBABWE - TONGOONA, PANGIRAI, 1992-1993 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS GHANA - UBOMBA-JASWA, SUSSANNA REGINA, 1992-1994 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS CHINA - WANG AI-WEI, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS CHINA - WANG JIAN, 1988-1991 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS CHINA - WANG YAN, 1990-1994 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS CHINA - WANG ZHENYUAN, 1986-1991, 1994 (Box R3059)
    - F-PS INDIA - WISEL, MOHIDEEN SHEIK, 1991-1993, 2004 (Box R3059)
    - F-HS THAILAND - WORACHART SIRAWARAPORN, 1985-1988 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - WU KUNSHENG, 1987-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - XU YONG, 1987-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-PS CHINA - YANG XIUSHI, 1988-1995 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - YE QIAOLUN, 1989-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - YU ZHIHONG, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-HS CHINA - ZHANG WANGGEN, 1988-1995 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZHANG YU, 1988-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZHAO YUAN, 1988-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZHONG GANYUAN, 1985-1994 (Box R3060)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZHONG HENG, 1989-1992 (Box R3061)
    - F-PS CHINA - ZHOU ZHONG-XUN, 1989-1994 (Box R3061)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZHU QUN, 1988-1996 (Box R3061)
    - F-AS CHINA - ZOU JI-TAO, 1989-1994; Complete file includes 9 folders, and 7 supplementary material folders across R3062-R3065. (Box R3061)